maketick.com 2018-06-26

# Privacy & Terms - tickto

## Tickto Privacy Policy

### How Our Services Work and What Information We Collect

When you use a mobile device that has Wi-Fi enabled, your device sends out a signal to nearby Wi-Fi networks. The signal that your mobile device sends include an identifier called a MAC address, which is a unique combination of numbers and letters associated with your mobile device. Tickto observes the information being sent by mobile devices, including the device’s MAC address, manufacturer, and signal strength. Tickto does not collect or use any personal information such as name, e-mail address, or phone number.

### How We Use and Share the Information We Collect

Our Customers: Tickto works with retailers and other customers to help them better understand customer behavior and provide better experiences for their customers. After receiving the non-identifiable data sent by mobile devices, Tickto applies a hash function to the MAC addresses to further anonymize them. Tickto analyzes the data it observes and provides aggregate anonymous information to our customers, such as retailers. For example, we may share information such as how many people visit a retailer’s store, how long people stay, how often they return, what sections of the store they visit, and whether customers visit other stores of the retailers’ locations. This non-identifiable information allows retailers to improve your shopping experience, including managing store inventory and employee staffing to improve customer service, and measure the effectiveness of marketing campaigns or store displays.

Service Providers: Tickto may engage third party service providers to perform functions on its behalf, such as hosting and analyzing data, in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Other Sharing: In addition to the above, we may also share information with third parties for the following reasons:

To allow a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets. If we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with an applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Tickto’s rights or property. If you expressly opt in to such sharing. How We Store the Data We Collect: We take reasonable security measures to protect your data while in transit and in storage. Data is encrypted while in transit and in storage. We hash MAC addresses before we store them, and we will not re-identify the data we collect. We retain data about individual hashed MAC addresses for 18 months, unless we have to keep the information for legal purposes. After 18 months, we only retain data about hashed MAC addresses in aggregate form.

Opt Out of Tickto’s Services: You can opt out of having Tickto collect data from your device by clicking here and inserting your MAC address. If you provide us with your MAC address to opt out of our services, we will retain that MAC address indefinitely in order to continue to effectuate your opt-out. For instructions on how to locate your MAC address, see below

Information Collected and Used on Tickto’s Website: We collect certain anonymous and personally identifiable information from you when you use our website. We only collect personally identifiable contact information from you when you explicitly provide it to us, such as through a request to receive more information about our products. We also collect certain anonymous and aggregate information about visitors to our website to better improve our services. We may use third parties to collect this anonymous and aggregate information, such as Google Analytics. We may share anonymous or aggregate information about our website visitors with third parties for advertising purposes, such as re-targeting, or with other trusted parties that assist us in operating our website or conducting our business. We may also share any information we collect from users of our website pursuant to the Service Providers and Other Sharing sections, above.

Privacy Policy Changes: Based on forthcoming situations, our privacy policy may change. Currently, the privacy policy, as we have provided above, is up-to-date and the usage of your information will be governed by the most current version of the guidelines. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. The current version is effective as of July 7, 2014.

Questions: If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@tickto.com.
